That was a video that we just imagined
as a team. What would it be like if we
lived through the decades? And because
of an amazing creative scrappy
resourceful team of
self-taught artists and creative
journalists, we were able to bring that
to life and then put it on our own
airwaves.
Millions of people watched it. We get to
publish this journalism to millions of
people because of YouTube. And because
of that we can get weird and we can come
up with new ways of showing how the
world works.
I grew up not really learning
information like the rest of the world.
I had to visualize it. Had to see it to
understand it. And with an amazing team,
we work together to try to make that
gift of understanding possible to
others.
So, I'm just so grateful that we could
honor that with this trophy and this
amazing team that we have here and all
over the world that work together. We're
trying to reimagine the future of
journalism on YouTube and we're really
excited to be here tonight. Thank you so
much.